<resources>
<string name="app_name">Fly-Fish Log</string>
    <string name="menu_app_name">Fly-Fish Log</string>

        <!-- Copyright (C) 2017  Carl Berberich -->

        <string name="app_name_beta">FishingLogBeta</string>
        <string name="add_coffee">Encryption Key</string>
        <string name="fishlog_title_label">Spring Fishing</string>
        <string name="fishlog_title_hint">Enter Stream Name</string>
        <string name="partners_title_hint">Latitude - Longitude</string>
        <string name="qsf_title_hint">Qty/Species/Fly</string>
        <string name="location_desc_hint">Location Description (access point)</string>
        <string name="fishlog_details_label">Details</string>
    <string name="select_for_export">Select for limited Exporting to file</string>

    <string name="select_export_label">Select for Export</string>
    <string name="select_send_Db_report">EXPORT limited Selection\n &amp; Save/Send Database as CSV file </string>
        <string name="hide_loc_label">Send Location Description and Hatch Notes in Report</string>
        <string name="hide_photo_label">Send Photo in Report</string>
        <string name="hide_db_label">Send Db in Fishlog Report</string>
        <string name="notes_hint">Hatch Notes:</string>
        <string name="date_picker_title">Date of Fishlog:</string>
        <string name="pause">Pause Location Updates</string>
        <string name="resume">Resume Location Updates</string>
        <string name="new_entry">Create NEW Log Entry</string>
        <string name="show_view">View MAP of List</string>
        <string name="show_subtitle">Count Entry Logs</string>
        <string name="hide_subtitle">Hide Count</string>
        <string name="subtitle_format">%1$d entries</string>
        <string name="water_temp_hint">Water Temp and Weather</string>
        <string name="delete_fishlog">4.Delete this Fishlog Entry</string>
        <string name="fishlog_receipient_text">Choose Receipient</string>
        <string name="fishlog_report_text">Send Fly-Fishlog Report</string>
        <string name="fishlog_report">Stream:%1$s\n The Fly-Fishlog was created on: \n%2$s. %3$s %4$s\n</string>
        <string name="fishlog_report_hidden">The Fly-Fishlog location is hidden </string>
        <string name="fishlog_report_not_hidden">The Fly -Fshlog location is not hidden</string>
        <string name="fishlog_report_no_receipient">there is no receipient</string>
        <string name="fishlog_report_receipient">the receipient is %s</string>
        <string name="fishlog_report_subject">Fly-FishLog Report</string>
        <string name="fishlog_Db_report">This is the complete Db</string>
        <string name="fishlog_database_subject">Fly-FishLog Database Report</string>
        <string name="send_report">Send Fly-Fishlog report via</string>
        <string name="fishlog_table">Fly-Fishlog table</string>
        <string name="fishlog_intro1">INTRO</string>
        <string name="fishlog_purpose">Help Page</string>
        <string name="send_Db_report">EXPORT All\n &amp; Save/Send Database as CSV file </string>
        <string name="import_Db_report">Upload Fly-FishLogBackup.csv</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Fly-FishLog</string>
    <string name="normal_map">MAP_TYPE_NORMAL</string>
    <string name="hybrid_map">MAP_TYPE_HYBRID</string>
    <string name="satellite_map">MAP_TYPE_SATELLITE</string>
    <string name="terrain_map">MAP_TYPE_TERRAIN</string>
    <string name="fishlog_intro">
        This application is for logging of technical fly-fishing trips with Google mapping support of the
        stream access points and locations on-stream. Users will be able to predict future insect
        hatches and fish behavior year to year by logging their current activities. The purpose is
        to improve fishing success by knowing what to expect during the year and where to fish from
        prior experience. \n\n

    By logging your fishing experience, it should give you the advanced knowledge for future fishing
    trips. Not every hatch occurs on every stream, nor does a hatch on a stream occur everywhere on a
        stream, nor does a hatch occur at exactly the same day each year. But history can repeat
        itself for insect behavior. By logging precise location information for specific hatches it can
        enhance your future fishing success rate. Building an information base is key to improving
        your flyfishing.\n\nObviously this application can be used for far more things than just fly fishing.
        \n\nCopyright © 2019 Driftless Software Solutions,  Version 1.27</string>

        <string name="importexport">
            <b><i>MORE INFO</i></b> \n
        1. WARNING:Keep your data secure and use encryption!  Create an Encryption Key using a word
        or phrase.  The same word/phrase used to Export (creating the file) must be used to Import
            and decrypt the same file into the database. If no Key is used, then the file will not be
        encrypted/decrypted and will be readable text. You do not have enrypt a file to use the
            import/export feature. This application uses 128-bit AES encryption. If you encrypt, be
            sure to record the key!!!\n\n
        2. By clicking the \'EXPORT All &amp; Save/Send Database as CSV file\' button (above),
        the database of logs will dump into a CSV file and can be emailed as an attachment to anyone
        you choose or saved to your My Drive, or sent via other applications. Most Android devices
        will require you to change your permissions to allow this to happen. Most importantly, you can
        use this feature to backup your data to yourself. \n\n
        3. By clicking the \'EXPORT Selection &amp; Save/Send Database as CSV file\' button (above),
        the database of only the Selected logs will dump into a CSV file and can be emailed as an attachment to anyone
        you choose or saved to your My Drive, or sent via other applications. Most Android devices
        will require you to change your permissions to allow this to happen. You can use this feature
        to send selected logs to another. \n\n

        4. IMPORT CSV button.\nWARNING:This feature is for advanced users. You could delete all your Log data.\n
        By clicking on the \'IMPORT CSV\' button (above), you will be directly uploading a file of
        Log data into the database from the Downloads directory.  Prior to IMPORT, you  must first download
            the file to your device.  Email appended files will download to the Download folder.
        To IMPORT, you must first select a RadioButton to Overwrite or to Append this data. Overwriting will drop
        (delete) all your current data from the database and then insert new data from this file.
        Appending will add this data to your existing database.\n\n
        To choose a file to import, click on the IMPORT Button, then select a CSV file from the Dialog
        screen and click Ok. This reads files that are currently in the Download folder. This import
            file must be a CSV file with the same type of data as in the
        EXPORT file. One way to generate an import CSV file that you can use, is by first using the
        EXPORT Button function to generate this file, and then emailing yourself the file. By
        opening this email on your device and saving the CSV attachment to the Downloads Directory,
        that file is now accessible (selectable) for importing.\n\n
        For Overwriting, it is extremely recommended to test the CSV data first by appending a sample
        of data prior to overwriting. Once data is deleted from the database, there is no recovery.
        If there is an error in the CSV data, this will cause major issues with your Database. Photos
        are not uploadable.\n\n

        5. If the download of the files is not working.  If you are unable to download the CSV file,
            it could be due to your email app has used up all available memory.  Sometimes, it will look
            like your file is stuck in the email app\'s Outbox.  To fix, you will need to clear out the
            memory for your email app on your device. For example, with GMail, you need to go to
            Settings -> Apps -> GMail -> Storage and click on CLEAR DATA.  Alternately, you can reboot
            your device.\n\n

        6. VIEW and DELETE Files (from menu).  This menu button will show all CSV files saved in the
        Download Storage folder. Selecting a file and choosing OK, will delete the file from Storage.
        \n\n</string>

    <string name="help_intro"><b>Select from the Menu on this page for a Help Item. There are 4 text pages and
    5 map pages plus advice on Cell Phone Connectivity.</b></string>

    <string name="purpose_new">Overview:This application is for the storage of fishing information.
    There are five pages in this application with the addition of five Google Maps routing/navigation
        pages:\n</string>

    <string name="intro">The <b>Intro page </b> (previous page) describes purpose and usage, and is the starting
        page to Help, Import/Export, and to the Log.</string>
    <string name="help"> <b>Help page </b> (this page) describes how the Logging application works and explains
        features.</string>
    <string name="import_export"><b>Import/Export Page</b> imports and/or exports your data via email. Delete
        is also supported. The following info is also found on the Import/Export page.  You can only
        import from the Download folder.</string>
    <string name="list"><b>List Page</b> shows a list of all Log entries with sorting abilities. Links to Detail
        Log page and Mapping. The Start button on the Intro page links to the List Page.</string>
    <string name="map_view"><b>\'View Map of List\'</b> (from List Page menu) shows a map with the
        current location and all GPS marked Entries in the current list (if you have logged GPS location data).</string>
    <string name="navigation"><b>Navigation - GoTo - using Google MAP\'</b> (from List Page Menu) allows the user
        to select from a list of logged locations and opens Google Maps to route you there. Offline Google
        Mapping is supported.</string>
    <string name="details"><b>Details Page</b> is the log for a particular entry. Tapping on any List page
        log entry takes you to the Details page of that entry.  Swipping left or right on a Details page, takes
        you to the next listed entry.</string>
    <string name="view"><b>View MAP - Details Page Map</b> is \'#3 View Map\' menu item of Details Page show map of logged area
        (if you have GPS location data).</string>
    <string name="loc_desc"><b>Location Description Map</b> is \'LOC LAT/LNG\' map page button.  This can generate
        the Location Field info (if service is available), accessed from the \'LOC LAT/LNG\' button
        from the Detail\'s page. This allows selection of a location from the shown map. </string>
    <string name="notes"><b>\'NOTES LAT/LNG\'</b> button page for the Notes field (if service is available).
        accessed from the \'NOTES LAT/LNG\' button from the Detail\'s page. This allows selection of location
        from the shown map.
    to name the location and save the LAT/LNG to the log</string>
    <string name="map_points"><b>How do you get Map points in your log and on your Google Maps?</b> </string>
    <string name="connectivity"><b>Cell Phone Connectivity </b> - Cell towers, wireless, and GPS. Do you need it?</string>

    <string name="intro2">
        <b><i>MORE INFO</i></b> \n
        1. Intro Page: From this page you can go to the Help Page or the IMPORT/EXPORT Page from the menu.\n\n
        2. Intro Page: From this page you can go to the List Page using the Start button.</string>

    <string name="list2">
        <b><i>MORE INFO</i></b> \n
        1. List Page:In this page you can add (create) new Log entries(from menu) or just view all of the previously added
        streams Log entries. You MUST add Log entries first, before viewing them. There will be no
        entries viewable until you add them. You can also view a map of all of your entries with
        routing navigation by Google Maps.(from menu)\n\n
        2. List Page:The purpose of the List Page is to show a list of Log Entries.  They are normally
        listed in Chronological descending order when no Radio buttons are checked.  The radio button \'Loc\'
        signifies all entries by their title in alphabetical order. The radio buttons Spring, Summer,
        Fall and Winter, reorganizes the list by their
        season in monthly ascending order, regardless of year. This allows for later comparisons of
        Log entries. Going back to the Intro page will clear all radio buttons.\n\n

        3. List Page: The \'Selected for Export\' Checkbox shows currently selected log entries that
        will be downloaded for the \'EXPORT limited Selection &amp; Save/Send Database as CSV file\'
        button (on the IMPORT/EXPORT page).  This feature is set by clicking on \'Select for limited
        Exporting to file\' Checkbox on the corresponding Log Detail page.\n\n

        4. List Page:To create a new entry you click on the \'Create NEW Log Entry\' menu button in the upper menu field.
        Clicking on the \'Create NEW Log Entry\' menu button will send you to the Details page, where you write the new
        data. You can also click the \'COUNT Entry Logs\' to view the total number of current entries.\n\n

        5. List Page: The \'View MAP of List\' menu shows locations of all the currently listed entries that
        have GPS data in the Location Field.  This Map page centers on your current location with Markers showing all
        entries Titles that have LAT/LNG for their Location Description (access point) data. Clicking on a
        Map marker enables the Google Map GO-TO routing navigation function from your current
        location.\n\n

        6. List Page: The \'Navigation - GoTo - using Google MAP\' menu item allows the user to select from the
        created list of Stream Name Locations (access point with LAT/LNG info) and then opens Google
        Maps to create a route to there.  If there is more than 1 Location Description for a \'Stream
        Name\', the user will be then given the choices. A user can also create a \'Home\' Name with
        a valid LAT/LNG info (by creating a Home log entry with LAT/LNG info), and this will show as the #1 Choice.
        Google MAPs will use Offline Google Maps by accessing your current Google Offline maps if
        you are offline and show this location. This provides navigation (routing) from your current location
        to this point.  It is required for you to prebuild your Google Offline maps to use this offline feature.\n\n

        7. List Page: The \'Sort by:Search for the Stream Name\' menu item allows the user to locate a specific
        listed entry or list of entries based upon the starting Stream Name letters.\n\n

        8. List Page: The \'Sort by:Search in QSF Data\' menu item allows the user to locate a specific
        listed entry or list of log entries based upon a selected input.\n\n

        9. List Page: The \'Sort by:Search in Notes Data\' menu item allows the user to locate a specific
        listed entry or list of log entries based upon a selected input.\n\n

        10. List Page:To open any current Details Page of an existing List entry, click(tap) on the
        particular entry on the List page to open it\'s Details page. All information on this
        Details page is directly editable.\n\n</string>

    <string name="map_view2">
        <b><i>MORE INFO</i></b> \n
        \'View MAP of List\' from the List Page menu shows locations of all the
        currently listed entries that have GPS data in the Location Field.  This Map page centers on
        your current location with Markers showing all
        entries Titles that have LAT/LNG for their Location Description (access point) data. Clicking on a
        Map marker enables the Google Map GO-TO routing navigation function from your current
        location.\n\n</string>

    <string name="navigation2">
        <b><i>MORE INFO</i></b> \n
        \'Navigation - GoTo - using Google MAP\' from the List Page menu item allows the user to select from the
        created list of Stream Name Locations (access point with LAT/LNG info) and then opens Google
        Maps to create a route to there.  If there is more than 1 Location Description for a \'Stream
        Name\', the user will be then given the choices. A user can also create a \'Home\' Name with
        a valid LAT/LNG info (by creating a Home log entry with LAT/LNG info), and this will show as the #1 Choice.
        Google MAPs will use Offline Google Maps by accessing your current Google Offline maps if
        you are offline and show this location. This provides navigation (routing) from your current location
        to this point.  It is required for you to prebuild your Google Offline maps to use this offline feature.\n\n</string>

    <string name="details2">
        <b><i>MORE INFO</i></b> \n
        1. Details Page:When creating a new Log entry from the List Page (Create NEW Log Entry menu button), the app
        will send you to a new Details Page which shows Hint information in each editable field.
        To save information in the Details page, data is saved after leaving that data field. Text
        can be added via the software keyboard or using the microphone (if enabled) located on the
        software keyboard\n\n

        2. Details Page Menu: The menu has 4 items.\n
        #1.\'Add Stream Name from current data\'\n
        #2.\'Add Loc Description from current data\'\n
        #3.\'View MAP\'\n
        #4.\'Delete this Fishlog Entry\'.\n
        The #1 and #2 menu items allow you to select data from a list of current Names or a list of current Locations.\n
        #3\'View MAP\' shows the log location in a Google Map.\n
        #4 \'Delete Log\', will delete the current log after confirmation.\n\n

        3. The #3\'View MAP\' menu selection (top of Details Page screen) opens a Google Map view centering on
        the LAT/LNG data found in \'Location Description\' Field. This centering point is displayed
        with a red marker. \nLAT/LNG data must be present or map will not be created and viewed. This
        GPS data can be gotten using the ADD LAT/LNG button or typed in with correct format as the
        GPS button provides. \nThe Map view can be zoomed into or out using the map +- buttons or your fingers.
        The Map also shows your current position with a blue circle or gotten by using the My Location
        Button(right corner).  \nYou can also move (scroll) the viewpoint of the map.  The compass feature
        is also enabled, allowing rotation of the map view.  \nAdditional Google Map Marks are added
        in the map for all Lat/Lng data found in \'Notes\'(also gotten using the GPS button
        for that field), signified by a blue marker. All marker names are the text directly before their
        LAT/LNG data from the Notes Field. Touching a marker on the map displays their marker name.  Touching a marker
        also opens the Google Maps mobile app controls in the lower right of the screen. This enables
        standard routing navigation to this marker from your current location. \nHaving a data connection,
        or wireless is necessary to view map information. This data is not available offline. \nThere is a
        menu at the top of the page allowing alternate views of the map page including a Satellite view.\n\n

        4. Details Page: You can use the current date/time as shown, or click the date field
        Button to select a different date.\n\n
        5. Details Page: The camera button (if available) on the Details Page takes a picture.
        After taking the picture, the picture is save to the application. Taking another picture overwrites
        the original.\n\n
        6. Details Page: Clicking on the picture\'s thumbnail image enlarges for enhanced viewing. These photos
        are private and cannot be shared. Use you regular camera application to take public photos.\n\n

        7. Details Page: The SAVE PHOTO Button will save the picture to the System\'s Photos\' Albums Directory,
        under Pictures\' folder.\n\n

        8. Details Page:The text field \'Location Description\' should be a written description about the
        access location. Typically this is where you accessed the stream and the direction of travel
        (upstream/downstream). LAT/LNG can be added. The Google Map marker name will be the text in
        the \'Location Description\' field. Use \'Create new Location Desc using Map\' from page menu
        to create this, or use \'Search for existing Location Descriptions\' to add exisiting loaction
        data.\n\n

        9. Details Page:\'LOC LAT/LNG\' button opens a Map to select a GPS Access Location. This is
        a Google MAP with crosshairs in the center of the screen.  This is the selected Lat/Lng. By
        moving the map (or using this current position) and selecting
        \'Add New Mark\' from this page\'s menu, you are selecting this Lat/Lng location to define your
        Access Location. The app will ask for a name for this access location. You can also select
        NORMAL, HYBRID, SATELLITE or TERRAIN menu items for viewing of the map prior to selecting \'Add New Mark\'.
        If wifi is not available Satellite and HYBRID Mapping displays is discouraged. Normal Mapping has the
        least data requirements, and quickest display to view.  If there is no WIFI or Cell Data connection,
        the current location GPS (LAT/LNG) can be saved, without showing a map.  If you have offline mapping,
        sometimes a map can be used.\n

        10. Details Page: Water Temp should be the current temperature where you are fishing. You could also add
        weather information.\n\n
        11. Details Page: Notes field should be a description of special things that you saw during your fishing.
        Including who you went fishing with, names of landowners, and telephone numbers.  All text
        written before a GPS LAT\LNG location will be used as that Marker name on Google Maps. Except,
        any text enclosed within parentheses will not be included in location Marker names. \n\n

        12. Details Page: The \'NOTES LAT/LNG\' button to the right of the \'Notes\' field, will add latitude
        and longitude info into the \'Notes\' field. This could require you to change your permissions
        to allow use your GPS on your phone. The app will ask for a name for this location. This will
        be the marker name for the latitude and longitude for your on-site location. Sometimes buildings or valley
        bottoms have blocked GPS satellite signals.
        This uses the same process as the \'LOC LAT/LNG\' from the Location Field. If there is no WIFI or Cell Data connection,
        the current GPS location (LAT/LNG) can be saved, without showing a map. If you have offline mapping,
        sometimes a map can be used.\n\n

        13. Details Page: If you select the \'Send Location Description and Notes in Report\' checkbox on the
        Details page, the \'Location Description\' field and \'Notes\' data will be in a
        Log Report, otherwise it is not included.\n\n

        14. Details Page: If you select the \'Send Photo in Report\' checkbox on the Details page, the photo will be in a
        Log Report, otherwise it is not included. On some devices, there is a limited amount of email
        storage cache.  If this is exceeded the device will not email until this the device is rebooted,
        or storage cache is cleared.\n\n

        15. Details Page: The \'Send FishLog Report\' Button on the Details Page will create and send an editable Log
        Report to any of your contacts that you choose via email or other applications (Google Keep,
        Google Drive, Message, etc). \n\n

        16. Details Page: The Checkbox for \'Select for limited Exporting to file\' is used by the IMPORT/EXPORT page.
        The Selected log entries will be the only items downloaded for the \'EXPORT limited Selection
        &amp; Save/Send Database as CSV file\'. This setting is also shown on the List Page, but is
        controlled on this page\n\n

        17. Details Page: You can directly view additional Details Pages by swiping on the page left or
        right (chronologically up or down in the default list).\n\n

        18. WARNING:To display maps, either a WIFI connection or Cell connection is required.
        Without cell data connection or a wifi connection maps could appear blank, only showing marks.
        Complete maps will be shown when you have a connection. This data is normally cached and once
        viewed can possibly be used for offline usage (until cache data is cleared).\n\n

        19. This application and it\'s data can be migrated to a new device using appropriate migration
        software. Check prior to wiping phone. It is recommended to save all log data by choosing to
        use the Import/Export feature, \'Save/Send Database as CSV file\' as a backup or prior to an update.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="view2">

        <b><i>MORE INFO</i></b> \n
        The #3\'View MAP\' from the Detail\'s menu button (top of Details Page screen)
        opens a Google Map view centering on
        the LAT/LNG data found in \'Location Description\' Field. This centering point is displayed
        with a red marker. \nLAT/LNG data must be present or map will not be created and viewed. This
        GPS data can be gotten using the ADD LAT/LNG button or typed in with correct format as the
        GPS button provides. \nThe Map view can be zoomed into or out using the map +- buttons or your fingers.
        \nThe Map also shows your current position with a blue circle or gotten by using the My Location
        Button(right corner).  You can also move (scroll) the viewpoint of the map.  The compass feature
        is also enabled, allowing rotation of the map view.  \nAdditional Google Map Marks are added
        in the map for all Lat/Lng data found in \'Notes\'(also gotten using the GPS button
        for that field), signified by a blue marker. \nAll marker names are the text directly before their
        LAT/LNG data from the Notes Field. Touching a marker on the map displays their marker name.  Touching a marker
        also opens the Google Maps mobile app controls in the lower right of the screen. This enables
        standard routing navigation to this marker from your current location. \nHaving a data connection,
        or wireless is necessary to view map information. This data is not available offline.\n There is a
        menu at the top of the page allowing alternate views of the map page including a Satellite view.\n\n</string>

    <string name="loc_desc2">
        <b><i>MORE INFO</i></b> \n
        \'LOC LAT/LNG\' button from the Detail\'s page opens a Map to select a GPS Access Location.
        If you have connectivity you will see a Google MAP with crosshairs in the center of the screen.  This center position
        is the selected Lat/Lng.\n\n By moving the map (or using this current position) and selecting
        \'Add New Mark\' to name this point from this page\'s menu, you are selecting this Lat/Lng location to define your
        Access Location. \n\nYou can also select NORMAL, HYBRID, SATELLITE or TERRAIN menu items for
        viewing of the map prior to selecting \'Add New Mark\'.\n\n
        If wifi is not available Satellite and HYBRID Mapping displays is discouraged.\n\n Normal Mapping has the
        least data requirements, and quickest display to view.\n\n
        If there is no WIFI or Cell Data connection, your current location GPS (LAT/LNG) can be saved,
        without showing a map.  If you have offline mapping,
        sometimes a map can be used.\n\n Only one mapping position is allowed in this field.  Selecting a
        second position overwites the original.\n\n</string>

    <string name="notes2">
        <b><i>MORE INFO</i></b> \n
        \'NOTES LAT/LNG\' button from the Detail\'s page opens a Map to select a
        GPS Access Location. If you have connectivity you will see a Google MAP with crosshairs in
        the center of the screen.  This is the selected Lat/Lng. By
        moving the map (or using this current position) and selecting \'Add New Mark\' to name this point from this page\'s menu,
        you are selecting this Lat/Lng location to define your Notes Location. \n\n
        You can also select NORMAL, HYBRID, SATELLITE or TERRAIN menu items for viewing of the map
        prior to selecting \'Add New Mark\'.
        If wifi is not available Satellite and HYBRID Mapping displays is discouraged. Normal Mapping has the
        least data requirements, and quickest display to view.  If there is no WIFI or Cell Data connection,
        your current location GPS (LAT/LNG) can be saved, without showing a map.  If you have offline mapping,
        sometimes a map can be used. You can have any amount of these locations in your Notes.\n\n</string>

    <string name="map_points2">To get your Location Access Mapping points, you use the LOC LAT/LNG button
        and the HELP instructions for Loc Desc - Detail page instructions. \n\n To get your Notes LAT/LNG
        Mapping points you use the Note\s LAT/LNG button and HELP instructions
    for it. </string>
    <string name="connectivity2">
        <b><i>MORE INFO</i></b> \n
          This app uses cellphone and wireless connectivity with it mapping abilities.  But it is not required
    to have cell tower connectivity.  It is required to have GPS reception. Which is found mostly universal outside.
        Having wireless connectivity allows the cellphone to have the fast data transfers.  High speed data transfers allows high
    resolution for satellite mapping.  Cell tower connectivity allows the next highest form of data transfer.
    This is not 100% required.  Google Maps provides offline mapping.  This is available directly from the Google Map
    app\'s menu.  You pre-download your map area prior to using it.  This works well for navigation, but
    not as well for Fly-Fish Log map viewing.  However, With no cell tower connectivity, if you have previewed
        the map, the data is now stored in current memory and is still available.\n\n
    This app being on an android phone can also work without a cell phone connection contract, by using a wireless
    connection.  This can be by connecting to a home wireless network, a commercial wireless network or another cellphone\'s
    wireless hotspot.\n\n
      </string>


    <string name="fishlog_start">Start</string>
    <string name="acknowledge">Acknowledgements</string>
    <string name="fishlog_acknowledge">Privacy Policy: At no time is any data collected from or
        about the user. Import/Export and Emailing or storage of data is at the sole discretion and responsibility of
        the user.\n\nI want to thank the Big Nerd Ranch group for their guidance,
        inspiration, and expertise in Android programming. I hope I got this right. Also to Google Maps for
        their amazing product, and to all the Fly-fisher people using this, \'Tight Lines\'.
    </string>



    </resources>
